California ephemera collection, 1860-
California Ephemera Collection,
- Townsend, Mrs. Stephen (Box 181)
  1. TOWNSEND, MRS. STEPHEN - PORTRAIT.
- Townsend, Stephen (Box 181)
  1. TOWNSEND, STEPHEN - PORTRAIT.
- Tracy, California (Box 104)
- Trade schools - California (Box 104)
- Trade shows (Box 249)
- Trade shows - California (Box 224)
- Trader Joe's (Boxes 104, 275)
  Box 104 - 2 folders.
- Trader Vic's. Emeryville, California (Box 287)
- Traffic flow - California - Los Angeles (Box 104)
- Trailfinders Club. Los Angeles. (Box 181)
  2 folders. 1. DAWSON, GLEN, 1912 -
- Transamerica Title Insurance Company (Box 181)
- Transit Coalition. Sylmar, California (Box 275)
- Transportation - California (Boxes 182, 287)
- Transportation - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 182, 199, 287)
- Travel Town. Los Angeles, California. (Box 212)
- Travis, Ezra Johnson (Box 104)
- Trinity County, California (Boxes 104, 275)
- Trona, California (Box 275)
- Tropico, California (Box 224)
- Truckee, California (Box 191)
- Tucker, Lorenzo, - 1986 (Box 104)
- Tulare County, California (Boxes 105, 275)
  Box 105 - 2 folders.
- Tule Lake Pilgrimage 2002 (Box 275)
- Tully, Jim (Box 105)
- Tunney, John Varick, 1934 - (Box 105)
  1. TUNNEY, JOHN VARICK, 1834 - PORTRAIT.
- Tuolumne County Water Company (Box 105)
  1. MINES AND MINERAL RESOURCES - CALIFORNIA - TUOLUMNE COUNTY. 2. ENGRAVINGS - SPECICIMENS.
  3. WATER DISTRICTS - TUOLUMNE COUNTY.
- Tuolumne County, California (Box 105)
  1. CALAVERAS COUNTY, CALIF.
- Turbine pumps (Box 189)
- Turlock, California (Box 105)
- Tustin, California (Box 249)
- Twentynine Palms, California (Boxes 105, 276)
- UCLA (Box 287)
- UCLA - Transportation (Box 287)
- UCLA Extension (Box 287)
- Ukiah, California (Box 105)
- Ultrasound Services (Box 276)
- Unarius Education Foundation. El Cajon, California (Box 224)
- Underwood Family Farms. Somis, California (Box 287)
- Unemployed Citizens Non-Partisan League. Pasadena, California (Box 183)
- UNESCO - Los Angeles. Los Angeles Public School controversy. (Box 140)
- Union Bank and Trust Company. Los Angeles. (Box 105)
- Union Oil Company of California (Box 105)
- United Farm Workers (Boxes 103, 183, 214)
  See also box 214. Box 214 is an oversize box.
  - Dear Los Angeles friend ... please don't buy grapes., ca. 1968(?).; Item No. 1 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    An open letter to Los Angeles supporters asking them for their continued support of the Grape Strike
  - You can help farm workers, don't buy grapes or Gallo wines., June 29, 1975.; Item No. 2 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Boycott for democracy ... boycott grapes unless you see this label., 1975.; Item No. 3 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Csar Chvez curriculum, a supplemental curriculum guide for classroom use 4-6, in conjunction with Safe Food & Justice For All Curriculum Guide, Grades K-12., 1995.; Item No. 4 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - A United Farm Workers Coloring Book = Libro para colorear de los Trabajadores Campesinos Unidos., undated.; Item No. 5 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - No grapes: poster for the videorecording., 1992.; Item No. 1 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    "We are killing ourselves, we are killing our children, we are destroying our earth. And this has got to stop."--Emilio Estevez. Video narrated by Mike Farrell.
- United Teachers Los Angeles (Boxes 251, 276)
- Universal City Studios (Boxes 225, 276)
- Universal City, California (Box 105)
- Universities and colleges - California (Box 186)
- Universities and colleges - California - Los Angeles (Box 183)
  Box 183 - 2 folders.
  - Mexican American Students Association, East Los Angeles College., 1968.; Item No. 2 (Box 183, Folder 2)
- Universities and colleges - California - religion (Box 183)
- University High School. Los Angeles, California. (Box 251)
- University of California, Berkeley. Regional Oral History Office. (Box 183)
  1. ORAL HISTORY.
- University of Southern California. Los Angeles. (Boxes 183, 287)
  Box 183 - 3 folders.
- Unruh, Jesse, 1922 - (Box 105)
- Upland, California (Box 189)
- Uplifters Club. Los Angeles, California. (Box 105)
- Urban planning (Box 249)
- Vacaville, California (Box 106)
- Valencia, California (Box 189)
- Valle, Ignacio Del, 1808 - 1880 (Box 105)
  1. VALLE, IGNACIO DEL, 1808 - 1880 - PORTRAIT.
- Valle, Reginaldo F. del, 1854 - 1938 (Box 105)
  X Dek Valle, Reginaldo F.
- Vallejo, California (Box 105)
- Vallejo, Maria Felipe Francisca Benicia (Carrillo) de, 1815 - 1891 (Box 105)
  [Wife of Gen. Mariano Guadalupe Vallejo.]
- Vallejo, Mariano Guadalupe, 1808 - 1890 (Box 105)
- Valyermo, California (Box 276)
- Van Dyke, Theodore Strong, 1842 - 1923 (Box 106)
- Van Nuys family (Box 106)
- Van Nuys, California (Box 106)
  1. LOS ANGELES
- Van Nuys, Isaac Newton, 1835 - 1912 (Box 106)
- Van Vogt, Alfred E., 1912 - (Box 196)
- Vandenberg Air Force Base (California) (Box 192)
- Vasquez Rocks, California (Box 106)
- Vasquez, Tiburcio, 1835 - 1875 (Box 106)
- Venice, California (Boxes 106, 199, 249, 262, 276)
  1. LOS ANGELES. Also oversize material. Box 249 - 2 folders.
  Box 199 is an oversize flat box. Box 262 is an oversize flat box, 22-1/2" x 28-1/2".
- Ventura County, California (Boxes 250, 276)
- Ventura, California (Boxes 212, 250, 276)
- Veterans - Los Angeles (Box 106)
- Veteran's Home Association. San Francisco. (Box 199)
- Veterans of Foreign Wars - United States - California (Box 106)
- Veterinary hospitals (Box 250)
- Veterinary medicine (Boxes 224, 287)
- Victor Valley, California (Box 106)
- Victorville, California (Boxes 250, 276)
- Vidaver, Henry, 1833 - (Box 106)
  1. VIDAVER, HENRY, 1833 - - PORTRAIT.
- Video tapes - catalogs (Box 191)
- Videogames - Exhibitions (Box 276)
- Videotapes - Catalogs (Box 276)
- Vigilance committees (Box 106)
- Village Weekly (Box 190)
  The Village Weekly. 1. WESTWOOD VILLAGE (WEST LOS ANGELES).
- Villaraigosa, Antonio (Box 276)
- Vischer, Edward, 1809 - 1879 (Box 106)
- Vista, California (Box 189)
- Visual Resources Group of the Los Angeles Area (Box 106)
  1. PHOTOGRAPHY - CALIFORNIA. 2. PHOTOGRAPHY - RESEARCH.append
- Vivisection - California (Box 191)
- von Grunebaum, Gustave Edward, 1909 - 1972 (Box 106)
- Voorhis, Horace Jeremiah (Jerry), 1901 - (Box 106)
- Voorsanger, Jacob, 1852 - 1908 (Box 106)
- Vroman, Adam Clark, 1856 - 1916 (Box 106)
  1. VROMAN, ADAM CLARK, 1856 - 1916 - PORTRAIT.
- Wagner, Henry Raup, 1862 - 1957 (Box 107)
- Wakoski, Diane (Box 107)
- Walnut Park, California (Box 195)
- Walt Disney Archives. Burbank, California (Box 107)
  X Disney Archives.
- Walt Disney Co. (Box 276)
- Walt Disney Studios (Box 192)
- Wanamaker, Marc, 1947 - (Box 107)
- War with Iraq. 2003 (Boxes 251, 277)
  2003
- Ward, Nelson, 1856? - 1948 (Box 107)
- Warner Hot Springs, California (San Diego County) (Box 107)
- Warners Ranch. San Diego County, California (Box 107)
  1. San Diego County, Calif. - History. 2. Butterfield trail.
- Warren, Earl, 1891 - 1947 (Box 107)
- Warren, William Crossman, 1837 - 1970 (Box 107)
- Warshaw, Howard, 1920 - (Box 108)
- Washing machines (Box 224)
- Watchorn, Robert, 1858 - 1944 (Box 108)
- Water Conservation (Box 277)
- Water Conservation - California (Box 250)
- Water Resources Development - California (Boxes 142, 163)
- Water Taxis (Box 224)
- Water, Drinking (Box 250)
- Waterman, Robert Whitney, 1826 - 1891 (Box 108)
  1. WATERMAN, ROBERT WHITNEY, 1826 - 1891 - PORTRAIT.
- Waters, Russell Judson, 1843 - 1911 (Box 108)
- Watkins, Carleton E., 1829 - 1916 (Box 108)
- Watsonville, California (Box 108)
- Watts Towers. Los Angeles, California.
  SEE: Los Angeles, Calif. - Watts Towers
- Watts, California (Boxes 108, 190)
  - The Watts Towers., 1961.; Item No. 1 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    Illustrated brochure about Simon Rodia's Towers in Watts (Los Angeles, Calif.) and how to visit them.
  - Watts Labor Community Action Committee., undated.; Item No. 2 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Watts feeds itself., ca. 1970.; Item No. 3 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    Illustrated pamphlet about the Watts Labor Community Action Committee (WLCAC). The WLCAC attempted to beautify Watts and generate jobs and pride in the community among residents. Pamphlet specifically describes programs in farming and agriculture.
  - Studio Watts., 1969.; Item No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    Folded, poster-size brochure including graphics, photographs, and articles related to the activities and mission of the Studio Watts Workshop. The Studio Watts Workshop was founded as a community arts organization by James Woods and Guy Miller in 1964. The original Workshop was located at 103rd Street and Grandee in South-East Los Angeles. The Studio Watts Workshop became the Watts Community Housing Corporation in 1969.
  - Guide to the Watts Summer Festival., 1967.; Item No. 5 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    Brochure with street map and guide to vendors and entertainment for the 1967 Watts Summer Festival.
  - The towers of Simon Rodia in Watts., undated.; Item No. 6 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Arson and street war: most destructive riot in U.S. history., August 27, 1965.; Item No. 7 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    Life magazine photographic essay, with accompanying text, documenting the Watts riots in Los Angeles (Calif.)
- Weather - California - Los Angeles (Box 192)
- Weaver, John Downing, 1912 - (Box 108)
- Weinstock, Harris, 1854 - 1922 (Box 108)
- Wellborn, Charles, 1867 - (Box 108)
  1. WELLBORN, CHARLES, 1867 - - PORTRAIT.
- Weller, John B., 1812 - 1877 (Box 108)
  1. WELLER, JOHN B., 1812 - 1875 - PORTRAIT.
- Wellstone, Paul, 1944-2002 (Box 277)
- Wendte, Charles William, 1844 - 1931 (Box 108)
- Wentz, Roby, 1909 - 1979 (Box 108)
- West Coast Father's Day Council (Box 277)
- West Hollywood, California (Boxes 195, 203, 251, 252, 259, 277)
  SEE ALSO: Sherman, Calif. Box 233 - 2 folders. Box 259 - 2 folders.
- West Hollywood, California - Churches (Boxes 233, 259)
- West Hollywood, California - Description and travel (Boxes 233, 259)
- West Hollywood, California Pacific Design Center. (Box 233)
- West Hollywood, California - Politics and government - 1998-1999 (Box 233)
- West Hollywood, California - Politics and government - 2000 (Box 259)
- West Hollywood, California - Restaurants, lunchrooms, etc. (Boxes 233, 259, 277)
- West Hollywood, California - Streets - Santa Monica Boulevard (Boxes 233, 259)
- West Los Angeles, California. (Boxes 250, 277)
- West, Nathanael, 1902 - 1940 (Box 108)
  1. WEST, NATHANAEL, 1902 - 1941 - PORTRAIT.
- Westchester, California (Box 277)
- Weston, Edward, 1886 - 1958 (Box 109)
- Westwood Art Association. Los Angeles, California. (Box 109)
- Westwood Charter School. Los Angeles, California. (Boxes 232, 277)
  Box 232 - 4 folders. SEE ALSO: Westwood Elementary School. Los Angeles, Calif.
- Westwood Elementary School. Los Angeles, California. (Box 204)
- Westwood Village. (West Los Angeles). (Boxes 184, 250, 277)
  Box 250 - 2 folders.
- Wheat, Lu, 1840 - 1909 (Box 109)
- Wheeler Springs, California (Boxes 109, 251)
  Wheelers Hot Springs, Wheeler Springs, Calif.
- Wheeler, Benjamin Ide, 1854 - 1927 (Box 109)
- Wheelers Hot Springs, California (Box 261)
- Whiskeytown-Shasta-Trinity National Recreation Area (California) (Box 277)
- White, Stephen Mallory, 1853 - 1901 (Box 109)
- White, Stewart Edward, 1873 - 1946 (Box 109)
- Whittier, California (Boxes 109, 261)
  Box 261 - Allied Gardens.
- Widney, Joseph Pomeroy, 1841 - 1938 (Box 109)
- Widney, Robert M. (Box 109)
- Wieczorek, Max, 1863 - (Box 109)
- Wiggam, Albert Edward, 1871 - (Box 109)
- Wiggin, Kate Douglas (Smith), 1856 - 1923 (Box 109)
- Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1875 - (Box 109)
- Wildlife - California (Boxes 109, 277)
- Wildlife conservation - California (Box 224)
- Will Rogers State Historic Park (Box 250)
- Willat, Irvin V., 1892 - 1976 (Box 109)
- William Andrew Clark Memorial Library. Clark Observatory. (Box 196)
- Williams, George, 1860? - 1948 (Box 109)
- Williams, Paul Revere, 1894-1980 (Box 277)
- Williamson, Frederick Warren, 1898? - 1942 (Box 109)
  Missing 12/19/97.
- Williamson, Robert Bruce (Box 109)
  1. WILLIAMSON, ROBERT BRUCE - PORTRAIT.
- Wilmington, California (Boxes 212, 277)
- Wilshire, Henry Gaylord, 1861 - 1927 (Box 109)
- Wilson, Harry Leon, 1867 - 1939 (Box 109)
- Wilson, Jackson Stitt, 1868 - (Box 109)
- Wilson, John Scott (Box 109)
  1. WILSON, JOHN SCOTT - PORTRAIT.
- Wilson, Mt. (Box 109)
- Winchester Mystery House. San Jose, California (Box 250)
- Windsor Square - Hancock Park Historical Association. Los Angeles, California. (Box 250)
- Wineries - California (Box 250)
- Winters, California (Yolo County) (Box 109)
- Wishon, California (Box 277)
- Wolfskill (William) Ranch House. Los Angeles County. (Box 109)
- Women - Societies and Clubs (Box 109)
- Women's Building (Los Angeles, California.) (Box 224)
- Women's Liberation Movement - California (Box 224)
- Wonder Valley, California (Box 277)
- Wood, Charles Erksine Scott, 1852 - 1944 (Box 109)
- Wood, John W., 1851 - 1934 (Box 109)
- Woodbury College. Los Angeles, California. (Box 110)
- Woodland Hills, California (Box 110)
  X GIRARD. LOS ANGELES COUNTY, CALIF.
- Woodland, California (Yolo County). (Box 110)
- Woody, Stonewall A., 1869? - 1948 (Box 110)
- Workman, William Henry, 1839 - 1918 (Box 110)
- Works, John Downey, 1847 - 1928 (Box 110)
- World Concert of Nations (Box 110)
- World War, 1939 - 1945 - California (Box 110)
- World War, 1939 - 1945 - California - Los Angeles (Box 110)
  X. LOS ANGELES ATTACKS.
- Wright, Frank Llloyd, 1867-1959 (Boxes 224, 250)
- Wright, Harold Bell (Box 110)
- Wright, Lloyd, 1890-1978 (Boxes 189, 213)
- Wright, Miss Beulah (Box 110)
  1. WRIGHT, MISS BEULAH - PORTRAIT.
- Wright, Willard Huntington, 1888 - 1939 (Box 110)
- Wrightwood, California (Box 110)
- Written Voice (Box 277)
  Literary journal
- Xeriscaping - California (Box 224)
- Xeriscaping - Santa Monica, California (Box 189)
- Y2K (Boxes 250, 277)
- Yarnell, Maurice A., 1860? - 1941 (Box 110)
- Yavno, Max (Box 110)
  1. YAVNO, MAX - PORTRAIT.
- Yoch, Florence (Box 110)
- Yolo County, California (Box 110)
- Yorba family (Box 110)
  1. YORBA, ANGEL, 1864? -1942 2. YORBA, ERNESTO TOMAS, 1871? - 1948.
- Yosemite National Park. California. (Boxes 111, 197, 250, 277)
  1. PARKS - CALIFORNIA. Box 197 - 3 folders.
- Young Men's Christian Association of Los Angeles (Box 184)
- Young Women's Christian Association. Los Angeles. (Box 184)
  X LOS ANGELES. YOUNG WOMEN'S CHRISTIAN ASSOCIATIONS.
- Young, Clement Calhoun, 1869 - (Box 184)
  1. YOUNG, CLEMENT CALHOUN, 1869 - - PORTRAIT.
- Young, William Henry, 1853 - 1942 (Box 184)
- Yountville, California (Boxes 250, 277)
- Yreka Western Railroad. Yreka, California (Box 250)
- Yuba County, California (Box 184)
- Yucaipa Valley, California (Box 184)
- Yucca Valley, California (Boxes 250, 277)
- Zeitlin, Jacob Israel, 1902 - (Boxes 184, 261)
  1. ZEITLIN, JACOB ISRAEL, 1902 - - PORTRAIT.
- Zeus, Carl C. (Box 184)
- Ziegner-Uriburu, J. (Box 184)
- Zoning - California - Los Angeles (Box 277)
- Zoological gardens - California, Southern (Box 111)